Stephen Thompson

Full-Stack Web Developer



LaGrange, Georgia, United States (770) 359-7037

thompson.stephen113@gmail.com

thompson-stephen113.github.io/portfolio-website/linkedin.com/in/stephen-thompson-790202241

EXPERTISE

- Node.js
- React/Bootstrap
- jQuery
- PostgreSQL
- Angular
- API
- AWS
- MondoDB
- Google Firebase

SUMMARY

Newly emerging web developer with previous experience in customer service and the live entertainment industry. Skilled in frontend web design and code management. Enjoys working in a collaborative environment as often as focusing on solo projects.

EDUCATION

Certificate in progress

May 2023 – present

CareerFoundry

Online education program with a focus in Full-Stack Web Development, taught over numerous reading and hands-on projects.

Bachelor's of Fine Arts, Design

August 2012 - May 2016

<u>& Technology</u>

Columbus State University

Degree with a focus in theatrical carpentry and scene design

TOOLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Python
- SQL
- JSON

EXPERIENCE

Barista

November 2020 - March 2023

Starbucks Coffee

Greeted customers in a timely and amicable manner while working in a rapid pace environment alongside other baristas. Maintained a clean and organized work environment to ensure optimal workflow and customer satisfaction.

Sea Lion Stagehand

April 2018 – September 2020

Georgia Aquarium

Acted as liaison between the Production, Sea Lion, and Wardrobe departments for costume management, requests, and appointments. Assisted animal trainers with their microphones and audio visual technician with microphone testing.

Garden Associate

March 2017 - October 2017

The Home Depot

Actively provided customers with useful information and assistance for their individual needs and projects. Took time to provide recommendations for other products as necessary for their purposes.

PROGRAMS

- Visual Studio Code
- Trello
- GitHub Desktop
- ChatGPT
- Postman
- pg Admin
- Windows PowerShell
- Android Studio
- Microsoft Office